http://www.perfectmind.com/policies/privacy

Privacy Policy
We take your privacy and security seriously.
Effective August 22nd, 2018
This privacy statement describes how PerfectMind, Inc. ("PerfectMind ) collects and uses the personal information you provide on our websites and platforms: PerfectMind and ChampionsWay. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information. The use of information collected through our service shall be limited to the purpose of providing the service for which the client has engaged PerfectMind.
What Kind of Information Do We Collect?
We collect information (such as your name, email address, mailing address, phone number, username and password, financial information such as your credit card number and billing address) that you provide when you sign up with us. We also maintain a record of your product interests and your purchases online.
How Do We Use Your Information?
When you make a purchase from us, we use your information to process your order. We will also send you email to confirm your order, and we may need to contact you via phone, postal mail or email if we have other questions regarding your order. When you register with us or participate in a contest or promotion you may choose to receive emails from us regarding our products, and services. From time to time, we may also send you email to help us learn more about your shopping preferences. In addition, we may use information about your product interests and purchases to help us improve our site design and your shopping experience.
How Do I Remove My Information?
We want to communicate with you only if you want to hear from us. If you prefer not to receive information from us, either through email, postal mail or by phone, please follow the unsubscribe instruction within the email message or contact us at support@perfectmind.com. Please note that such requests may take up to 2 weeks to become effective. In addition, if you ask us to remove your name and address from our email or postal mailing lists, we will maintain your name in a "do not mail" file to ensure that we can honour your request. Please also note that when you make a purchase, we will send you emails to confirm your order and may also need to contact you via phone, postal mail or email if we have other questions regarding your order.
Information Sharing
We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as processing your credit card or offering customer support through a chat service. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us. We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement. We do not sell your personal information to third parties. We may also disclose your personal information:
In certain situations, PerfectMind, Inc. may be required to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements. as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request. if PerfectMind is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our website of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.
Facebook Connect
You can log in to our site using sign-in services such as Facebook Connect. This service will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information with us such as your name and email address to pre-populate our sign up form. Services like Facebook Connect give you the option to post information about your activities on this website to your profile page to share with others within your network.
How Do We Protect Kids' Privacy?
Consistent with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998, we will never knowingly request personal information from anyone under the age of 13 without prior verifiable parental consent. If we become aware that a subscriber is under the age of 13 and has registered without prior verifiable parental consent, we will remove his or her personally identifiable registration information from our files.
Information Collected for Our Customers
PerfectMind acknowledges that you have the right to access your personal information. PerfectMind collects information under the direction of its customers, and has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal data it processes. PerfectMind works with its customers to help them provide notice to their clients concerning, the purpose for which personal information is collected. If you are a client of one of our Customers and would no longer like to be contacted by one of our Customers that use our service, please contact the Customer that you interact with directly. PerfectMind may transfer personal information to companies that help us provide our service. Transfers to subsequent third parties are covered by the provisions in this Policy regarding notice and choice and the service agreements with our customers PerfectMind has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal data it processes. An individual who seeks access, or who seeks to correct, amend, or delete inaccurate data should direct his query to the PerfectMind's customers (the data controller). If the customer requests PerfectMind to remove the data, we will respond to their request within 30 business days. PerfectMind will retain personal data we process on behalf of our Customers for as long as needed provide services to our Customer. PerfectMind will retain and use this personal information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.
What Are Tracking Technologies?
As is true of most web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information may include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data.
We may combine this automatically collected log information with other information we collect about you. We do this to improve site functionality and improve the services we offer you.
PerfectMind and its partners use cookies or similar technologies to analyze trends, administer the website, track users’ movements around the website, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. You can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level, but if you choose to disable cookies, it may limit your use of certain features or functions on our website or service.To manage Flash cookies, please click here:
Manage Flash cookies.
Behavioural Targeting / Re-Targeting
We partner with a third party to either display advertising on our Web site or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third party partner may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on this site and other sites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you interest-based ads, you may opt-out by clicking here Please note this does not opt you out of being served ads. You will continue to receive generic ads.
We partner with a third party to either display advertising on our Web site or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third party partner may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on this site and other sites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you interest-based ads, you may opt-out by clicking here Please note this does not opt you out of being served ads. You will continue to receive generic ads.
Third Party Sites and Links
You may see various links throughout our site that lead to you another website, outside of www.perfectMind.com and www.championsway.com . These sites may include our affiliates, partners, or other sites that we believe are useful resources to our visitors. Because these links are to third party sites, PerfectMind perfectMind.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or any privacy issues that may arise on the third party sites. Please refer to the respective third party site for their privacy policies.
How Do We Make Sure Your Order Information Is Secure?
The security of your personal information and our clients' information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as log in credentials) we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).
We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our website, you can contact info@Perfectmind.com.
Testimonials
With your consent we may post your testimonial along with your name. If you want your testimonial removed please contact us at info@PerfectMind.com.
Social Media (Features) and Widgets
Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.
Data Retention
We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at info@Perfectmind.com. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.
Access to Personal Information
Upon request PerfectMind will provide you with information about whether we hold any of your personal information. If your personal information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, amend, delete/remove or deactivate it by making the change on our member information page, by emailing our Customer Support at info@Perfectmind.com or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below. We will respond to your request within a reasonable timeframe not longer than 30 days.
Notification of Privacy Policy Changes
We may update this privacy policy to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.
Questions or Additional Information
If you have questions regarding this agreement or wish to obtain additional information, please send an email to info@PerfectMind.com or you can send mail to 4333 Still Creek Drive, 2nd Floor Burnaby, BC Canada V5C 6S6.
COMPANY
About Us
Our Story
We're Hiring
Contact
Blog
SUPPORT
Knowledge Base
PerfectMind Inc. All Rights Reserved.
×
